<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Know it Owl</string>
    <string name="btn_start_learning">Start Learning</string>
    <string name="btn_start_admin">Administration</string>
    <string name="btn_start_statistic">Statistics</string>
    <string name="btn_start_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="btn_start_help">Help/About</string>
    <string name="btn_admin_new_card_new_stack">New Stack</string>
    <string name="btn_admin_new_card_existing_stack">Existing Stack</string>
    <string name="btn_learn_dynstack">Create dynamic Stack</string>
    <string name="btn_learn_sure">Sure</string>
    <string name="btn_learn_notsure">Not sure</string>
    <string name="btn_learn_dontknow">Do not know</string>
    <string name="btn_admin_newcard">New Card/Stack</string>
    <string name="btn_admin_editcard">Edit Card</string>
    <string name="btn_admin_delete_card">Delete Card</string>
    <string name="btn_admin_editstack">Edit Stack</string>
    <string name="btn_admin_importexport">Import/Export</string>
    <string name="btn_admin_newdynstack">New dyn Stack</string>
    <string name="btn_admin_create_dynamic_stack">Create dyn. Stack</string>
    <string name="btn_admin_update_dynstack">Update dyn Stack</string>
    <string name="btn_admin_save">save</string>
    <string name="btn_help_introduction">Introduction</string>
    <string name="btn_help_learnstatistics">Learn/Statistics</string>
    <string name="btn_help_editcardsstacks">Edit Card/Stack</string>
    <string name="btn_help_importexport">Import/Export</string>
    <string name="btn_settings_testdata">Write Test Data</string>
    <string name="btn_settings_reset_drawers">Reset Answers</string>
    <string name="btn_settings_reset_statistics">Reset Statistic</string>
    <string name="btn_settings_cleanup_pictures">Clean up Pictures</string>
    <string name="btn_help_about">About</string>
    <string name="btn_diagram">Show Diagram</string>
    
    <string name="title_activity_help_screen">Help/About</string>
    <string name="title_activity_help_screen_introduction">Help - Introduction</string>
    <string name="title_activity_help_screen_learn_statistics">Help - Learn/Statistics</string>
    <string name="title_activity_help_screen_edit_cards_stacks">Help - Edit Card/Stack</string>
    <string name="title_activity_help_screen_settings">Help - Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_help_screen_import_export">Help - Import/Export</string>
    <string name="title_activity_help_screen_about">Help - About</string>
    <string name="title_activity_admin_screen">Administration</string>
    <string name="title_activity_stapel_screen">Select Stack</string>
    <string name="title_activity_new_card">New Card</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_admin_edit_stack">Edit Stack</string>
    <string name="title_activity_admin_choose_stack_screen">Select Stack</string>
    <string name="title_activity_learning_card">Learning</string>
    <string name="title_activity_admin_import_export">Import/Export</string>
    <string name="title_activity_admin_edit_card">Edit Card</string>
    <string name="title_activity_admin_create_dynamic_stack">Create Dynamic Stack</string>
    <string name="title_activity_admin_edit_dynamic_stack">Edit Dynamic Stack</string>
    <string name="title_activity_statistics_screen">Statistics</string>
    
    <string name="statistics_screen_tab_overview">Overview</string>
    <string name="statistics_screen_tab_progress">Progress</string>
    <string name="statistics_screen_tab_lastreview">Last Review</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_help">Help</string>
    <string name="menu_start_screen">Home</string>
    <string name="admin_screen_tab_card_front">Card Front</string>
    <string name="admin_screen_tab_card_back">Card Back</string>
    <string name="admin_screen_tab_card_tags">Card Tags</string>
    <string name="admin_export">Export</string>
    <string name="admin_import">Import</string>
    <string name="learning_screen_tab_card_back">Card Back</string>
    <string name="learning_screen_tab_card_front">Card Front</string>
    <string name="content_start_screen_logo">know it owl Logo</string>    
    <string name="show_learn_counter">x/xx</string>
    
    <string name="error_handler_delete_db">Delete Database?</string>
    <string name="error_handler_general">An Error has occurred</string>
    <string name="error_handler_import_error">Import Error</string>
    <string name="error_handler_name_taken">Name already exists</string>
    <string name="error_handler_no_sd">No SD Card available</string>
    <string name="error_handler_no_input">Please insert a name</string>
    <string name="error_handler_no_tag">No Tags selected</string>
    <string name="error_handler_file_not_found">File not found</string>
    <string name="error_handler_export_error">Export Error</string>
    
    <string name="text_help_introduction">Know it Owl helps you to organize your learning cards for school, university or for fun. You are always informed of your learning progress. You can exchange know-how in terms of pictures, text, videos or easily in terms of links. Share your learning cards/ knowledge with your friends and profit from theirs. That is the way how you can know it All/Owl.</string>
    <string name="text_help_learn_statistics">How do you start learning?\n \n You can start learning when you at least already have added one learning card (For an explanation how to do this, go back and choose the help button EDIT CARDS/STACK). \n \n If you already have added learning cards ,choose START LEARNING and then choose one stack. After that the FRONTside of the first learning card will be displayed. You can give an answer without looking at the BACKside of the card by left wiping. \n \n If you are 100 % sure about the answer, push the left lower button (checkmark). If you are not sure about the answer, but you have a clue, push the middle lower button (questionmark). \n\n If you definitely do not know the answer, push the right lower button (cross). \n \n Meanwhile the statistic will save your results and that is why in the next learning round in the same stack specific cards you were sure about and also specific cards you were not sure about, will be sorted out depending on the Leitner’ learning principle. \n \n If you want to start a new learning round from the whole beginning without buffered results in the background, you have to go to the main menu point SETTINGS. Then you just push the button RESET ANSWERS. \n \n When you want to track your learning progress you can see the statistics in two ways: \n \n At the end of each learning-round you are automatically shown your recent learning results in the tab LAST REVIEW also available out of the STATISTICS menu.There you see the duration of the learning process and you have the comparison of your recent to your last learning results concerning how many cards you did not know(dn), how many cards you were not sure(ns) about and how many cards you were sure(s) about. \n \n Second way is to click on the main menu point STATISTICS, where first of all you get an overview of the number of all cards of every stack you did not know, you were not sure about and you were sure about. In the next step you can choose a certain stack and then you only get the number of cards (for dn, ns and s) for the specific stack. In the next tab PROGRESS it is shown the last (at a maximum of 10) learning results of the different learning trials for the chosen stack. The last tab LAST REVIEW is already described before. :)  </string>
    <string name="text_help_settings">With the functionality SETTINGS (same name in the main menu), you are able to do 5 things. \n \n You can RESET your whole DATABASE with all your learning stacks you created before, \n \n or you only RESET all your given ANSWERS of every learning-round in every stack to start learning from the whole beginning with all cards. If you only want to manipulate one learning stack and not all, you can edit or delete it in the ADMINISTRATION main menu point and then select EDIT STACK. Important to mention is that by RESETING your ANSWERS, the STATISTICS data is not influenced. That means that your learning progress will be recorded further. \n \n That is why you need to push the button RESET STATISTICS when you also want to start a new learning progress in the STATISTICS. \n \n Next thing you can do is CLEANING UP all your taken PICTURES at once by clicking CLEAN UP PICTURES. \n \n At last you have the choice to generate test Data for you first walk trough to become comfortable with the handling of Know it Owl.</string>
    <string name="text_help_import_export">If you want to share your learning cards with friends or make a data back-up you can export or import learning cards as follows: Push the button ADMINISTRATION and after that select IMPORT/EXPORT. \n \n You have the choice to export a stack in 2 ways: \n \n a) If you switch to the tab EXPORT you can export by longer touching a specific stack. If you want to export multiple stacks at once, you better create a dynamic stack before with all the stacks included. Therefore you go to the main menu point ADMINISTRATION and then choose NEW DYN STACK. \n For exporting a chosen stack you can select whether your data in the form of a xml-file should be transferred to your Dropbox account, to another gadget over Bluetooth or wi-fi direct or you are able to send your data to your or another one’s email account. \n To make sure that your data is exported correctly you can see all successfully transferred exports in the tab IMPORT. The IMPORT side serves as an archive. \n \n b) You also can export a stack by going to ADMINISTRATION, then EDIT STACK, then longer touching the stack item and at last pushing ARCHIVE. \n \n You have the choice to import a stack also in 2 ways: \n \n a) From the IMPORT tab you can import a stack again, if you have exported it before you potentially deleted it under ADMINSISTRATION, then EDIT STACK, DELETE. \n \n b) When you received a learning stack in the form of a xml-file from a friend, for IMPORTING you need to directly open your xml-file with Know it Owl (Open With…). The imported xml-file will be saved automatically and you can START  LEARNING with the new stack in the main menu. </string>
    <string name="text_edit_cards">If you want to build a new stack with learning cards, please follow these instructions: \n \n Choose ADMINISTRATION and after that push the button NEW CARD/STACK. Then you are able to fill the card with text by simply clicking in the textfield. If you also want to add a picture or a hyperlink, use the little attachment icon below. Same for the backside of the card. At last you have the possibility to add one or more tag names to your card. With the help of tags you later can create dynamic stacks, which include different cards from different tags. Well, after you have created your front and backside, you can add the card to an EXISTING STACK or to an NEW STACK. \n \n You can also change your properties for an already built stack under ADMINISTRATION and then EDIT STACK: After you have selected a stack by longer touching the item, you can \n \n - CHANGE the NAME, \n - RESET ANSWERS for all the cards of the specific stack, \n - ADD TAGS TO ALL CARDS of this stack, \n - DELETE the stack or ARCHIVE the stack.\n \n If you only want to edit a single card or some more cards in a stack, you have to go to the main menu point START LEARNING and after that you need to switch to the specific card you want to edit. There you find in the mobile menu (left lower button) the menu point EDIT CARD or DELETE CARD.</string>
    <string name="text_choose_stack">Choose Stack:</string>
    <string name="text_hyphen">-</string>
    <string name="text_dont_know:">Don\'t Know:</string>
    <string name="text_sure:">Sure:</string>
    <string name="text_not_sure:">Not Sure:</string>
    <string name="text_acutal_status">Actual Status:</string>
    <string name="text_dont_know">Don\'t Know</string>
    <string name="text_sure">Sure</string>
    <string name="text_not_sure">Not Sure</string>
    <string name="text_no_data_available">No Data Available</string>
    <string name="text_date">Date</string>
    <string name="text_total_time">Total Time:</string>
    <string name="text_number_of_cards"># of Cards:</string>
    <string name="text_last_runthrough">Last Runtrough:</string>
    <string name="text_stack_name">Stack Name:</string>
    <string name="text_duration">Duration:</string>
    <string name="text_status_before">Status before:</string>
    <string name="text_status_after">Status after:</string>
    
    <string name="lbl_help_about_version">Version 1.0</string>
    <string name="lbl_help_about_feedback">Feel free to rate this App and send us your Feedback</string>
    <string name="label_settings_resetdatabase">Reset Database</string>
    <string name="lbl_name">Name: </string>
    

</resources>